<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfNewsItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Rawalpindi mega projects to be completed during PM Khan’s tenure: Sh Rashid</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi   -  Federal Minister of Interior Sheikh Rashid Ahmed said that the mega projects including Mother Child Hospital, Leh Expressway and Ring Road to be completed during the tenure of Prime Minister Imran Khan.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:20:42 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Exam system being reformed on modern lines, says minister</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI   -  Punjab Minister for Higher Education and Information Technology Raja Humayun Yasir Sarfaraz on Monday said that plans were being made to reform the examination system on modern lines.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:19:49 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Govt to bring Sialkot tragedy’s culprits to justice: Noor ul Haq</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  -   The Federal Minister for Religious Affairs and Interfaith Harmony Pir Noor ul Haq Qadri has said that the lynching of Sri Lankan Manager Priyantha Kumara in Sialkot is a shameful act.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:18:42 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>LHC rejects bail plea of illegal housing society’s owner</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI   -  The division bench of Lahore High Court (LHC) on Monday rejected bail plea of owner of an illegal housing society involved in storming along with armed goons into the premises of judicial complex and clashing with opponents.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:16:36 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Rawal Dam Chowk Interchange project  to be completed by June 2022</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  Capital Development Authority (CDA) Chairman Amer Ali Ahmed Monday visited various ongoing development projects in the federal capital and reviewed progress work.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:16:12 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Armed clash leaves one dead, protesters  block GT Road for hours</title>
    <description>Islamabad   -  An armed clash broke out between two groups over land dispute in Bhangrail area of Sihala on Monday, leaving one dead and three injured, informed sources.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:15:53 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>State owned institutions cannot do real estate business: IHC</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  The Islamabad High Court (IHC) Chief Justice Athar Minallah Monday remarked that the state owned institutions cannot do real estate business as it is clearly a matter of conflict of interest.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:15:06 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>NIH confirms Omicron variant in Karachi</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -   National Institutes of Health (NIH), Islamabad has been able to confirm (via whole genome sequencing) that a recently suspected sample from Karachi is indeed the &amp;lsquo;Omicron variant&amp;rsquo; of SARS-CoV2.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:14:43 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>RPO awards commendation certificates, cash prizes among best cops</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI  -   Regional Police Officer (RPO) Rawalpindi Ashfaq Ahmad Khan awarded commendation certificates cash prizes among best performing officers and cops in the year 2021.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:14:28 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Knowledge platform launches Parhai Buddy</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  Knowledge Platform, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s leading edTech venture announced the launch of Parhai Buddy, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s first Artificial Intelligence (AI) powered learning coach.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:13:52 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Firing on school van  severely injures driver</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi   -  Two masked gunmen opened indiscriminate firing on a school van in Mohammadi Colony at Adiala Road on Monday, injuring the driver critically, informed sources.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:13:36 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Graduation ceremony held at PAF Finishing School</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  The graduation ceremony of the 50th batch of Pakistan Air Force (PAF) Finishing School was held at   Air Force Complex.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:13:13 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Anti-polio drive kicks off in Rawalpindi</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI   -  Deputy Commissioner (DC) Muhammad Ali on Monday inaugurated the five-day anti-polio drive by administering drops to children under five years of age here at Basic Health Unit, Kotha Kalan, Morgah.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:12:52 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>One more dies, four new Covid cases in 24 hours</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI   -   One more patient had died with fatal coronavirus during the last 24 hours, taking the total death toll to1606 in Rawalpindi district.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:12:33 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>33rd PNEC Convocation held</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  -   The 33rd Convocation Ceremony of Pakistan Navy Engineering College (PNEC) was held here on Monday where Chief of the Naval Staff Admiral Muhammad Amjad Khan Niazi graced the occasion as Chief Guest.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 6:12:12 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Two held for aerial firing, uploading video on social media</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI  - Police Monday arrested two persons on the charges of aerial firing, dis&amp;shy;playing weapons and uploading its videos on social media, informed po&amp;shy;lice spokesman.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 3:27:16 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>‘PML-N used NAB for vested interests’</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  - Special Assistant to the Prime Minister on Capital Development Authority Ali Nawaz Awan Mon&amp;shy;day said the last government of Pakistan Muslim League-Nawaz (PML-N) had used the National Accountability Bureau (NAB) for vested interests.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 3:26:57 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Rain likely in various parts of country: PMD</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Rain with snowfall is expected in up&amp;shy;per Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, Islam&amp;shy;abad, Potohar region, Kashmir, Gilgit Baltistan and its adjoining hilly areas during the next 24 hours, according to the Pakistan Meteorological De&amp;shy;partment (PMD).</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 3:22:47 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan has always stood by its Afghan brothers, sisters: FO Spokesperson</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Foreign Office Spokesper&amp;shy;son Asim Iftikhar Ahmad Monday said that host&amp;shy;ing of the OIC Council of Foreign Ministers (CFM) meeting on December 19 to consider the humani&amp;shy;tarian situation in Afghan&amp;shy;istan was continuation of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s resolve to stand by its brothers and sisters.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/14/2021 3:21:55 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Govt-controlled institutions cannot do real estate business: IHC</title>
    <description>Chief Justice Islamabad High Court Athar Minallah has said that said that ministries and the institutions working under government cannot indulge in real estate business as it will be considered a clash of interests.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 1:47:34 PM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>China seeks Pak coop in monitoring meteorological disasters</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - China sought cooperation from Pakistan and other Asian countries in monitoring, warning meteorolog&amp;shy;ical disasters as it will help a lot in minimizing grave effects, according to China Economic Net (CEN).</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 3:34:13 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>IHC to resume hearing in contempt of court case against former chief judge GB, others today</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Islamabad High Court (IHC) will Monday (today) resume hearing in a contempt of court case against former chief judge of Gilgit-Baltistan (GB) Rana Shamim and others for publishing a controversial affidavit of the former.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:10:41 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Stuntman Rajab Ali enthrals audience at IIUI</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Rajab Ali, a talented stuntman yesterday showcased his talent at the new campus of International Islamic University Islamabad (IIUI) where his unbelievable skills and agility were lauded by a huge crowd of students and university employees.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:09:28 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Islamabad to have Pakistan’s largest Ferris wheel soon</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Capital Development Authority (CDA) is all set to launch another entertainment initiative for the citizens of Islamabad as Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s largest Ferris wheel with a height of about 180 feet has been planned for installation at the Lake View park here.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:08:46 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>3-day Divvy Film Festival 2021 concludes</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Three-day Divvy Film Festival 2021 concluded here at Pakistan National Council of the Arts (PNCA) organized by Foundation Art Divvy in collaboration with PNCA.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:08:21 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Turkish cooking classes on Dec 20</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Islamabad Marriot Hotel would organise Turkish Cooking Classes from December 20.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:08:01 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>3-day food festival ‘Taste Plus’ concludes</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - A three-day food festival featuring food and music titled &amp;ldquo;Taste Plus&amp;rdquo; concluded here at Jinnah Convention Center on Sunday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/13/2021 2:07:42 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police bust gang involved in kidnapping children, forced begging</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi   -   New Town police busted a gang involved in kidnapping children and forcing them into begging in many parts of province.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:15:51 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police book director of illegal housing society over threatening police officer</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi   -  Chontra police have booked a director of illegal housing society on charges of hurling life threats towards a police officer and his son on phone call, informed sources on Saturday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:15:17 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Commissioner directs RDA to prepare  green regulations</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi   -   Commissioner/ Acting Director General (DG) Rawalpindi Development Authority (RDA) Gulzar Hussain Shah has directed Metropolitan Planning and Traffic Engineering (MP&amp;amp;TE) Directorate to prepare green regulations for intensification and restoration of ecosystem through maximization of Pothohari flora.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:14:52 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>‘Corruption weakening country’s roots’</title>
    <description>ATTOCK   -  Deputy Commissioner Attock Imran Hamid Sheikh has said that corruption is weakening our country&amp;rsquo;s roots.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:12:19 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Traffic rules awareness walk held in Attock</title>
    <description>ATTOCK   -   A rally in connection with traffic rules awareness was organized in Attock which was led by Deputy Commissioner Attock Imran Hamid Sheikh to inform the public about the traffic rules.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:11:42 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>3 persons jailed for abducting 16-year-old boy</title>
    <description>ATTOCK    -   Three persons were awarded imprisonment for attempting to molest a 16-year-old boy.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 6:11:19 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>IG Islamabad deputes 800 additional cops in police stations to meet force shortage</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - An additional strength of 800 cops have been deputed in 22 police stations of capital with the pur&amp;shy;pose to combat crime effectively and promptly address public com&amp;shy;plaints, informed a police spokes&amp;shy;man on Saturday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 3:22:37 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>CDA, PIDE to conduct joint study to check traffic congestion </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  - The Capital Development Authority (CDA) has decided to conduct a joint study in collaboration with Pakistan Institute of Development Economics (PIDE) to check traffic congestion in the city.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 3:21:59 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Tarnol police fail in netting 5 men involved in raping teenager</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - A teenage girl was allegedly gang-raped by five men in a house located at Mirchan Stop, in&amp;shy;formed sources on Saturday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 3:21:29 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Govt to finalise steps for digital census in Dec 2022: Amin</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The federal government would come up with practical outcomes in the next week to ensure conducting a digital population census by December 2022.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/12/2021 2:52:24 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>IHC summons Attorney General, CDA chairman and SAPM in person over Margalla Hills encroachments </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Islamabad High Court (IHC) Friday directed the Attorney General, the Chairman Capital Development Authority (CDA) and the Special Assistant to the Prime Minister on Climate Change to appear before the court in person in a matter related to the encroachments at Margalla Hills National Park.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:42:44 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>British High  Commission, Information Ministry jointly host  red carpet premiere</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The premiere of one of the biggest movies since the pandemic, James Bond: No Time To Die, was jointly hosted by British High Commissioner Christian Turner and Minister for Information and Broadcasting Fawad Chaudhry at the Islamabad Club, the British High Commission said yesterday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:42:21 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>ECP demands 3900  Electronic Voting Machines for election of mayor</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Election Commission of Pakistan (ECP) in a letter to the Ministry of Science and Technology has demanded 3,900 Electronic Voting Machines (EVMs) for the election of mayor in Islamabad.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:41:59 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>IG suspends 3 officers on charges of illegally detaining 5 persons </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Inspector General of Police (IGP) Islamabad Muhammad Ahsan Younas has suspended three police officials including Station House Officer (SHO) Police Station (PS) Secretariat on charge of illegally detaining five innocent citizens here on Friday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:41:35 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>PM second honest leader after Quaid-i-Azam: Ghulam Sarwar</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi-Federal Minister on Aviation Ghulam Sarwar Khan on Friday said that Prime Minister Imran Khan is the most honest leader after founder of Pakistan Quaid-i-Azam Muhammad Ali Jinnah, who kept identifying the corrupt people and launched legal action against them.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:40:57 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>SSP Traffic forms  6 teams to prevent accidents in capital</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - To ensure smooth flow of traffic and keeping in view road safety rules, SSP Traffic Islamabad Muhammad Omar Khan has formed six teams of surveillance and enforcement squads to prevent accidents and ensure the implementation of traffic rules, informed a police spokesman.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:40:33 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Challan ticket issued by motorway police helps investigators arrest kidnapper</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - A fine ticket issued by an officer of National Highways and Motorway (NHMWP) M2 (Islamabad) to a motorist for over-speeding led the investigators of Bhakkar police to bust a notorious kidnapping gang, members of which had abducted a businessman and received ransom of Rs2 million, informed sources on Friday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:40:15 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>African envoys visit PAEC  institutes </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The envoys of four African countries including Tunisia, South Africa, Kenya, and Sudan visited the two institutes of Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission - Pakistan Institute of Engineering and Applied Sciences and Pakistan Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:39:55 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Into the woods</title>
    <description>Usama bin Murad&amp;rsquo;s creative whimsies seem to invite art lovers with aesthetics eyes to walk right into an exhibition pregnant with pieces of wooden furniture on display.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:39:29 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Man battered in  F-9 Park</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - A consultant of Benazir Income Support Program (BISP) was clubbed and injured critically by an unknown attacker in F-9 Park, informed a police spokesman on Friday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:36:38 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Shifa International, SIMAP arrange  first surgical  instruments show</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Shifa International Hospital and the Surgical Instruments Manufacturers Association of Pakistan (SIMAP) arranged the first surgical instruments exhibition at Shifa here.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/11/2021 1:36:18 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan Water Week 2021 successfully concludes in Islamabad</title>
    <description>Up to 4,000 delegates from 20 nationalities pledged at the concluding session of the Pakistan Water Week 2021 (PWW) in Islamabad on Thursday to fight the looming water crisis.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:02:46 PM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Cold and dry weather likely in most parts of country; PMD</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  -   Pakistan Meteorological Department (PMD) Thursday forecast cold and dry weather for most parts of the country during the next 24 hours.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 6:29:06 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Academia can add value to national  narrative on Kashmir dispute: Shehryar</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Chairman of Parliamentary Committee on Kashmir Shehryar Khan Afridi Thursday urged the world community to take notice of the travesty of justice being committed by Indian occupational forces against the political prisoners of Jammu and Kashmir.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:20:55 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>‘Pakistan well aware  of regional and int’l  human rights  responsibilities’ </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Speaker National Assembly Asad Qaiser and Deputy Speaker Qasim Khan Suri have said that Allah Almighty has made man the noblest of creatures and has given him a complete code of life to live by.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:20:33 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>ITP issued 5,489 fine tickets over wrong parking during ongoing year</title>
    <description>Islamabad-The Islamabad Traffic Police (ITP) fined 5,489 vehicles over wrong parking during ongoing year and also impounded most of them in police stations creating problems in smooth flow of traffic, informed a police spokesman on Thursday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:20:08 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Man allegedly murdered in Kohsar Town</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The investigators of Homicide Investigation Unit (HIU) of Police Station (PS) Bhara Kahu have launched investigation into an application lodged by a woman accusing unknown persons for killing her brother and hanged the body, informed sources on Thursday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:19:51 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police arrest pick-pocket </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Bhara Kahu responded quickly over a public complaint and arrested a pick-pocket besides recovering looted amount from his possession, said a police spokesman on Thursday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:19:32 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>US embassy nominates ASP Amna Baig for prestigious award </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - US Embassy Charg&amp;eacute; d&amp;rsquo;affaires Angela P Aggeler yesterday hosted an event to mark the 30th anniversary of the 16 Days Against Gender Based Violence campaign.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:19:13 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Littering, wildfire serious threats to Margalla Hills’ flora and fauna</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Margalla Hills National Park&amp;rsquo;s flora and fauna is exposed to serious threats of survival due to regular fire incidents and carefree visitors who hurl waste everywhere.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:18:37 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>SSP investigation holds open court</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi-Senior Superintendent of Police (SSP) Investigation Syed Ghazanffar Ali Shah held an open court here on Thursday at CPO office which was attended by a large number of citizens.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:18:09 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>2 persons killed in separate incidents</title>
    <description>Attock-Two persons died in two different incidents.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:17:49 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>ICCI calls for  making conducive policies for persons with disabilities</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - President of Islamabad Chamber of Commerce and Industry (ICCI) Muhammad Shakeel Munir Thursday said that collaborative efforts are required for ensuring the inclusive, accessible, and sustainable future of persons with disabilities (PWDs).</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:17:18 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Amin lauds Korean, Chinese govts’ interest in PM Imran Khan’s green initiatives</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Hailing the participation of China and Korea in the country&amp;rsquo;s historically largest afforestation programme of Prime Minister Imran Khan, Special Assistant to PM on Climate Change Malik Amin Aslam on Thursday said the government was committed to work with global community to tackle adverse fallouts of the global warming on lives.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:16:57 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Rs100,000 fine imposed on   2 brick kilns</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - Rawalpindi District administration, in its drive to control the spread of smog, imposed a fine on two brick kilns in the area of Saddar here Thursday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:15:43 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Shop sealed, fine imposed for profiteering, violating COVID-19 SOPs   </title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - Assistant Commissioner (AC) Khauta on Thursday imposed Rs15,500 fine on shopkeepers in different areas of the tehsil Kahutta for indulging in profiteering.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:15:22 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>All available resources being utilised for welfare of people: MNA Tahir Sadiq   </title>
    <description>ATTOCK  - All available resources are being utilised for the welfare of the people and development of the Attock district.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/10/2021 12:15:00 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>What will be fate of Ord 2009 when Ord 2010 declared ultra vires, asks SC</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The Supreme Court of Pakistan Wednesday asked the Attorney General for Pakistan (AGP) to as&amp;shy;sist that when the Sacked Em&amp;shy;ployees (Reinstatement) Act, 2010 was declared ultra vires then what would be the fate of the Ordinance 2009 through which majority of the affected employees were reinstated.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 7:58:15 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan says ‘thanks’ on US invitation to virtual summit</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Pakistan has responded to the United States diplomatically by neither confirming nor refus&amp;shy;ing to attend the virtual two-day Democratic Summit by US Presi&amp;shy;dent Joe Biden starting today.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 7:57:34 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>India yet to respond to Pak decision to allow New Delhi aid to Afghanistan</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The government of India has not yet responded to the deci&amp;shy;sion of the government of Paki&amp;shy;stan which permitted transpor&amp;shy;tation of 50,000 tons of wheat and medicine to Afghanistan via Wagha border.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 7:56:30 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan reports 9 more Covid deaths, 310 infections</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Pakistan has recorded another nine deaths and 310 infections from the coronavirus pandemic during the last 24 hours (Tuesday), showed the figures released by the National Command and Operation Centre (NCOC) on Wednesday morning.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 7:50:02 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Vaccination certificate  compulsory for registration of  vehicles, token fee payment</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The ICT administration has made compulsory complete vaccination certificate for new registration of vehicles and payment of token fee of vehicles at the Excise and Taxation office after 15 December 2021.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:20:53 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Court summons Noor Mukaddam’s  father to record his statement</title>
    <description>Islamabad-The Additional and Sessions Judge (West) Islamabad Muhammad Atta Rabbani on Wednesday issued notice to former diplomat Shaukat Ali Mukaddam summoning him for recording his statement in Noor Mukaddam murder case on December 15.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:20:34 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Chinese govt gifts 7,000 saplings</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD -The Chinese government on Wednesday gifted 7,000 saplings of different species to support Imran Khan&amp;rsquo;s globally-acclaimed Ten Billion Tree Tsunami Programme and his Clean Green Pakistan vision.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:20:16 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan’s first-ever European Film Festival begins</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The premiere of the first-ever European Film Festival was held at Pakistan National Council of Arts Islamabad yesterday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:19:56 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Former CTO Rwp and son accused of land grabbing, illegal construction</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi-Police have forwarded a case of alleged land grabbing involving a former chief traffic officer and his son to deputy commissioner for further action, informed sources on Wednesday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:19:20 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Low cost plastic waste recycling machines receive overwhelming response at IIUI</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The state-of-the-art technology based low cost projects for recycling of plastic waste material displayed by the students of five leading universities during a function held at auditorium of International Islamic University Islamabad (IIUI) on Wednesday morning became source of attraction for visitors from national and international.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:18:57 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Martyrs pride  of Islamabad  police: IG  Ahsan Younas</title>
    <description>Islamabad-Inspector General of Police (IGP) Islamabad Muhammad Ahsan Younas said the police martyrs were pride of Islamabad police and welfare and care of their families is his personal responsibility.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:18:40 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Nuclear security is a national responsibility: Speakers</title>
    <description>Islamabad-The Center for International Strategic Studies (CISS) organized a conference titled &amp;lsquo;Strategic Stability and Nuclear Security: Global and Regional Perspectives&amp;rsquo; at the National University of Sciences and Technology (NUST).</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:18:20 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police arrest suspected robber during exchange of fire   </title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI- Police have arrested a suspected robber in injured condition after an exchange of fire in Shalley Valley and recovered weapons from his possession, informed a police spokesman on Wednesday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:17:54 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Protesting teachers assure opening schools today   </title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - The joint action committee of teachers on Wednesday submitted the demand to delete the relevant sections of local government ordinance which place FDE and educational institutions under the administrative control of mayor.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/9/2021 1:17:21 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Dr Junaid Ahmed, author of book 'Creation of Bangladesh; Myths exploded' delivers lecture at QAU </title>
    <description>Dr Junaid Ahmed, author of book "Creation of Bangladesh; Myths exploded" today delivered a talk at QAU Islamabad.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 5:24:07 PM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan records another 232 Covid-19 cases, 7 deaths</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD-Pakistan has recorded another seven deaths and 232 infections from the Coronavirus pandemic during the last 24 hours (Monday), showed the figures released by the National Command and Operation Centre (NCOC) on Tuesday morning.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:43:32 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Court grants time to defence for preparation in Lok Virsa reference</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - An Accountability Court (AC) on Tuesday granted time to defence for case preparation till December 21 in reference against Senator Robina Khalid and others pertaining to irregularities in Lok Virsa funds.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:42:52 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>PM tasks ecological restoration of River Indus through  stakeholder engagement: Amin</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Special Assistant to the Prime Minister (SAPM) on Climate Change Malik Amin Aslam on Tuesday said the Prime Minister in Climate Change Committee meeting has tasked all relevant quarters to initiate ecological restoration of River Indus through stakeholder engagement.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:42:21 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>ITP accelerate crackdown against vehicles having tinted glasses, fancy number plates</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Islamabad Traffic Police (ITP) has accelerated crackdown against the vehicles having tinted glasses, fancy number plates and hampering smooth flow of traffic due to wrong parking.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:41:24 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police recover 1.8kg drugs during raid   </title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - Police have arrested a drug pusher and recovered more than 1.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:41:04 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>‘Artist Talk, Art Exhibition’ held   to mark Jinnah’s   146th birthday</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Pakistan National Council of the Arts on Tuesday paid a tribute to father of the nation Muhammad Ali Jinnah in an Artist Talk and Art Exhibition to mark his 146th birth anniversary.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:40:45 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Socio-economic mainstreaming of women in Pakistan, Afghanistan crucial: Dr. Sania</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD - Special Assistant to the Prime Minister on Poverty Alleviation and Social Protection, Senator Dr.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:40:06 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Over Rs8b allocated for PP-1 Attock in 3 years: Yawar</title>
    <description>Attock-Provincial Minister for Social Welfare and Baitulmal Syed Yawar Abbas Bukhari has said that during the last three years, more than Rs8 billion have been allocated for different development projects for the development of his constituency PP-1 Attock and prosperity of its people.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:39:46 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>3 criminals wanted in  murder cases arrested</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - Police have arrested three proclaimed offenders wanted in heinous crimes from different areas, informed police spokesman here Tuesday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:39:27 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Dengue surveillance teams visit 8.9m sites in 6 months</title>
    <description>Rawalpindi-As many as 1757 teams under ongoing indoor and outdoor surveillance campaign have inspected 8,945,414 sites in various areas of the district from June to November this year.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:39:11 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Christmas cake cutting ceremony held at HFH church   </title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - A Christmas cake cutting ceremony was held here at Holy Family Hospital (HFH) Church here on Tuesday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:38:49 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>4 more dengue patients land in allied hospitals   </title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI - Four more patients were tested positive for dengue at two public sector hospitals of Rawalpindi city during last 24 hours raising the tally of confirmed cases to 3780.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:38:25 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police arrest 2 accused on abduction, rape charges   </title>
    <description>WAH CANTT - Police on Tuesday claimed to arrest two of the four accused who allegedly abducted a dancer, gang raped her and snatched money from her.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/8/2021 12:38:03 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Police fail to arrest robbers, victims await recovery</title>
    <description>A gang of four robbers while brandishing sophisticated weapons stormed into a house located near heavily guarded Red Zone in capital and made off with gold, cash, other valuables, leaving an impression that police exist nowhere, informed sources on Tuesday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 6:16:05 PM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Ahsan Younas appointed new IGP Islamabad</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD  -  The government on Monday has appointed Deputy Inspector General (DIG) Operations Lahore Muhammad Ahsan Younis as Inspector General of Police (IGP) Islamabad, informed sources.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:54:53 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>RCB issues final vacation notices to private schools</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI    -  The high ups of Rawalpindi Cantonment Board (RCB) on Monday issued final notices to some 496 private educational institutions, operating in residential areas to vacate the buildings and shift to commercial areas before December 31, 2021, informed sources.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:53:55 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>FIA recovers ETBP property from encroachers</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI   -   A team of Federal Investigation Agency (FIA) retrieved property of Evacuee Trust Property Board (ETPB) from encroachers in an operation in Sarafa Bazaar, informed sources on Monday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:53:31 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Ten more diagnosed with Covid</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI  -  Ten more people were tested positive for the deadly corona virus during the last 24 hours in the district, with four belonging to the Taxila, two from Rawalpindi Cantonment and Rawal town each; while one each case has arrived from Kahutta and AJK.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:52:56 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>IHC ex-judge  accuses former CJP  of ‘witch-hunt’</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  Islamabad High Court (IHC) ex-judge Shaukat Aziz Siddiqui Monday contended before the Supreme Court of Pakistan that he was removed as a judge of the Islamabad High Court (IHC) without holding an inquiry on the allegations, he made in his speech.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:52:30 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan Water Week kicks off to explore sustainable ways in climate crisis</title>
    <description>ISLAMABAD   -  The Pakistan Water Week 2021, a four-day international conference aimed at bringing together academics, government officials, NGOs, and policy experts from home and abroad to discuss the water issues facing the country begins on Monday.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:52:03 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>DC holds ‘Khuli Kutchery’ to resolve problems of citizens</title>
    <description>RAWALPINDI  -   Deputy Commissioner (DC) Rawalpindi Muhammad Ali on Monday held a &amp;lsquo;Khuli Kutchery&amp;rsquo; at his office with an aim to resolve problems of the people at the earliest.</description>
    <newsChannel>nation.com.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>12/7/2021 5:51:18 AM +05:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Soft Inaugural Ceremony of Pakistani-German Facilitation and Reintegration Center</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lahore:A soft inaugural ceremony of Pakistani-German Facilitation and Reintegration Center was held at the Overseas Pakistanis Foundation regional office, Lahore in continuation/progression to the MoU that was signed between the Deutsche Gesellschaft für Internationale Zusammenarbeit (GIZ) GmbH on behalf of the German Federal Ministry for Economic Cooperation and Development (BMZ) and the Overseas Pakistanis Foundation [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/soft-inaugural-ceremony-pakistani-german-facilitation-reintegration-center/"&gt;Soft Inaugural Ceremony of Pakistani-German Facilitation and Reintegration Center&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>10/16/2020 11:11:01 AM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>International Day of Rural Women: Hidden Force Of Country.</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;By: Durre Shahwar The first International Day of Rural Women was observed on 15 October 2008 according to the united nations . The purpose of the day is to recognize the efforts of rural women to improve society and the economy.According to the research 48 percent of rural women of Pakistan are contributing their efforts. Most of [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/international-day-of-rural-women-hidden-force-of-country/"&gt;International Day of Rural Women: Hidden Force Of Country.&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>10/14/2020 3:30:56 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Pakistan must honor pledge in Jinnah’s 11 August speech, HRCP</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lahore, 11 August. Observing National Minorities Day, the Human Rights Commission of Pakistan (HRCP) has said that both state and society must be true to Mr Jinnah’s vision of a country in which religion or belief was a personal matter and no basis for differences of citizenship. Seventy-three years after this historic speech, Pakistan’s religious [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/pakistan-must-honor-pledge-jinnahs-11-august-speech-hrcp/"&gt;Pakistan must honor pledge in Jinnah’s 11 August speech, HRCP&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>8/12/2020 1:13:32 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>GC University opens its doors for transgenders</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;LAHORE: (August 08, 2020) The Government College University Lahore has allocated special seats to transgenders for admissions to its undergraduate programs to increase the access of this underprivileged community to the higher education. GCU Vice Chancellor Prof. Dr Asghar Zaidi said that universities are a catalyst for change and GCU need to bring a change [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/gc-university-opens-doors-transgenders/"&gt;GC University opens its doors for transgenders&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>8/8/2020 3:57:11 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>UNDP organizes Digital Hackathon find solutions for Climate Change disasters and COVID-19</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;June 07 2020, Karachi:  The United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) concluded the Sindh segment of the “Master the Disaster” Digital Hackathon for Disaster Risk Reduction today– the second in a series of online hackathons held in partnership with Concepts Unlimited. The first was held in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa.The hackathon aimed to generate innovative ideas related to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/undp-organizes-digital-hackathon-find-solutions-climate-change-disasters-covid-19/"&gt;UNDP organizes Digital Hackathon find solutions for Climate Change disasters and COVID-19&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>6/8/2020 12:42:29 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Land mark decision on announcing 2% edu quota for religious minorities by GoP</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;As minorities living in Pakistan we appreciate the Punjab cabinet that approved 2% higher education quota for religious minorities in the Government higher education institutes of the province, a move lauded by many.  Among religious minorities, Christians are the largest minority of the Punjab province. Data from various cities in the Punjab shows an overwhelming [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/land-mark-decision-of-the-announcement-of-the-2-edu-quota-for-the-religious-minorities-by-gop/"&gt;Land mark decision on announcing 2% edu quota for religious minorities by GoP&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>5/22/2020 8:35:20 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Waziristan ‘honour’ killings barbaric, condemnable</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lahore, 17 May. The Human Rights Commission of Pakistan (HRCP) strongly condemns the cold-blooded murder of two teenage girls in a Waziristan village—allegedly an ‘honour’ crime carried out by a family member after a mobile video of the victims surfaced on social media. Despite the passage of the Criminal Law (Amendment) (Offences in the Name [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/waziristan-honour-killings-barbaric-condemnable/"&gt;Waziristan ‘honour’ killings barbaric, condemnable&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>5/17/2020 8:53:21 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Reconstitution of National Commission for Minorities</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;#160; The Federal Cabinet of Pakistan has reconstituted a National Commission for Religious Minorities in May 2020.  The tenure of the commission will be for a period of three years.  The new commission will comprise two Muslims, three Hindus, three Christians and one member each from the Sikh, Parsi and Kailash communities, while its chairman will [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/reconstitution-national-commission-minorities/"&gt;Reconstitution of National Commission for Minorities&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>5/13/2020 9:01:53 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>Funding and stone breaking of a church by Muslim scholars/Ulema in Multan.</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;By: Kamran Saeed A great example of religious harmony in Multan, all religions and sects, including Muslim Ulema, contributed to the building of the church. At the request of the Christian community, sacks of cement were purchased and handed over to them. The foundation of the church was laid by Muslim scholars (Ulema). Journalist for [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/funding-and-stone-breaking-of-a-church-by-muslim-scholars-ulema-in-multan/"&gt;Funding and stone breaking of a church by Muslim scholars/Ulema in Multan.&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>4/12/2020 12:39:24 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem>
    <title>بھائی چارے سے بڑا اور کوئی مذہب نہیں</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ازقلم: محمد توقیر رضا سومرو ملتان: ملک میں ہم آہنگی کو فروغ دینے کے لئے بہت سے لوگ اپنے طور پر ایسی مثالیں قائم کر جاتے ہیں کہ ان کے ساتھ رہنے والے لوگ اور آگے آنے والی نسلیں ہم آہنگی اور بھائی چارے سے متعلق بہت کچھ سیکھ جاتی ہیں۔ ایسی ہی ایک مثال [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk/no-religion-i-bigger-than-brotherhood/"&gt;بھائی چارے سے بڑا اور کوئی مذہب نہیں&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.newslens.pk"&gt;News Lens Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    <newsChannel>www.newslens.pk</newsChannel>
    <publishedDate>4/7/2020 10:44:46 PM +00:00</publishedDate>
  </NewsItem>
</ArrayOfNewsItem>